<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<!-- Optional: if Fair Fast Travel is still installed, redirect its guide entry to ours -->
	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_fair_fast_travel">
		<text>Fair Fast Travel</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_fair_fast_travel_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Fair Fast Travel is disabled when using %c[pda_yellow]Dorn's Fast Travel%c[ui_gray_1] (see guide).\n
			\n%c[pda_white]Open %c[pda_yellow]PDA Guide > Addons > Dorn's Fast Travel%c[pda_white] for how animated PDA travel works in this modpack.
		</text>
	</string>

	<!-- Dorn's Fast Travel guide -->
	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_dorn_fast_travel">
		<text>Dorn's Fast Travel: Addon Overview</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_dorn_fast_travel_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Dorn's Fast Travel%c[ui_gray_1] replaces instant map teleport with an animated journey inside the current zone. Right-click a destination on your PDA map to see travel options.\n

			\n%c[pda_green]GETTING AROUND\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]%c[pda_yellow]Travel here%c[ui_gray_1]: normal pace on the PDA route bar. No ruble fare.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]%c[pda_yellow]Sneak here%c[ui_gray_1]: about 1/3 map speed (3x longer), better ambush dodge chance, and a longer ambush pull-back.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Same-zone only for animated travel. Cross-zone trips need a %c[pda_yellow]zone exit%c[ui_gray_1] or %c[pda_yellow]Hire guide (instant)%c[ui_gray_1] on the map (rubles, no journey or survival drain).\n

			\n%c[pda_green]PDA MAP SPEED AND TIME\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Journey time follows PDA map speed, not a separate timer. Default fastest pace is 50 (about 1 game hour per km at normal weight).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]%c[pda_yellow]Encumbrance%c[ui_gray_1] slows the bar: yellow near-max weight (-25%), red overweight (speed divided by carry ratio).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Game time does not tick while the PDA bar moves. It jumps once at arrival (or partially on ambush). Hunger, thirst, and sleep follow that jump only вЂ” sneak costs more because the jump is longer.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Cancel journey: no time jump, no survival cost. You return to where you started.\n

			\n%c[pda_green]AMBUSHES\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Travel is blocked if hostiles are within 50 m (horizontal, 10 m vertical).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]During a trip, ambush %c[pda_yellow]scan radius%c[ui_gray_1]: 50 m day base, minus 10 m dawn/dusk, minus 20 m night, minus weather (rain 10 m, storm 15 m, foggy 20 m вЂ” stacks; not dodge chance).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]%c[pda_yellow]Dodge chance%c[ui_gray_1]: base value plus Scouting skill; Sneak mode doubles it. Weather does not change dodge chance.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]If an ambush triggers, you are pulled back by scan radius (Г—2 sneaking, max 60 m). Normal-travel ambushes cut stamina to half. Hostiles are alerted 1 s after you arrive; you are invulnerable until then.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Clear arrivals spawn 5 m before the destination.\n

			\n%c[pda_green]PDA ROUTE LINE\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]A dot path is drawn when travel starts (grey ahead, green behind). Dots every 20 m along the engine route.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Right-click anywhere on the PDA map during travel and choose Cancel journey (Back/Esc also works).\n

			\n%c[pda_green]SETTINGS\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_1]Tune options in %c[pda_yellow]MCM > Dorn's Fast Travel%c[ui_gray_1]: fastest PDA map speed, ambush dodge base, guide fees, and more.\n

			\n%c[pda_white]Good hunting, stalker!
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
