<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_fair_fast_travel">
		<text>Fair Fast Travel</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_fair_fast_travel_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]Fair Fast Travel is replaced by %c[pda_yellow]Dorn's Fast Travel%c[ui_gray_1].\n
			\n%c[pda_white]See %c[pda_yellow]PDA Guide > Addons > Dorn's Fast Travel%c[pda_white] for how travel works.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_dorn_fast_travel">
		<text>Dorn's Fast Travel</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_addons_dorn_fast_travel_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_1]
			\n%c[pda_yellow]Dorn's Fast Travel%c[ui_gray_1] lets you skip the tedium of (some) travel while retaining some risk and immersion.\n

			\n%c[pda_green]HOW TO TRAVEL\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Open the PDA map and %c[pda_yellow]right-click%c[ui_gray_2] a destination - bases, campfires, zone exits, or your own stashes (works with anomalous stashes).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[pda_yellow]Travel here%c[ui_gray_2]: Can only be used on the current map. %c[pda_yellow]Free. Fast. 30 minutes per km%c[ui_gray_2]. You will be  %c[pda_red]ambushed%c[ui_gray_2] by any hostiles you meet along the way.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[pda_yellow]Sneak here%c[ui_gray_2]: Can only be used on the current map. %c[pda_yellow]Free. Slow. 3 hours per km%c[ui_gray_2]. You have a chance to avoid hostile encounters. Has a short cooldown (shown on PDA map).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[pda_yellow]Hire guide%c[ui_gray_2]: Hire a guide to safely and instantly take you to any base or stash in the game - he will also help you carry your stuff so there's no weight ristriction. %c[pda_yellow]RU per km (scales with danger, see below), Instant. 1 hour per km%c[ui_gray_2].\n

			\n%c[pda_green]PDA SHOWS YOU JOURNEY\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]The PDA map shows the journey you're taking along a real path across the map. You can see the intended path in grey, and watch it change to green as you make progress.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Sneaking progresses much slower than normal travel on the PDA which matches the time that will pass when your journey is complete.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Simply close your PDA to cancel your journey.\n

			\n%c[pda_green]TRAVEL EFFECTORS\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Cannot travel during an emission.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Cannot travel when hostiles are too close.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Cannot travel when you are over encumbered (matches when you cannot move normally).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]20% slower when carry weight is yellow (within 10 kg of max carry weight).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]50% slower when carry weight is red (over max carry weight) and you will end travel with 10% stamina.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Taking any damage will cancel an in-progress journey.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]You must keep your PDA open for the duration of the journey.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Guide cost scales with distance and how dangerous the to/from locations are (approx double Fair Fast Travel's cost).\n

			\n%c[pda_green]AMBUSHES\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]During normal travel, hostiles can ambush you within your %c[pda_yellow]outer ambush range%c[ui_gray_2] (60m base; +10m when not sneaking). You are dropped on the path to confront them. Outer range needs %c[pda_yellow]line of sight%c[ui_gray_2].\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]An %c[pda_yellow]inner range%c[ui_gray_2] at %c[pda_yellow]50%% of outer%c[ui_gray_2] also ambushes you even without line of sight (behind cover, around corners).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Outer range is reduced by environment:\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Time: Night -20m (7pm-7am), and -10m in the hour before/after night.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Weather: Rain -10m, Storm -15m, Fog -20m.\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Your base sneak chance is 25%, but is increased by your Sneaking level (3%% per level,  max dodge chance is 85%).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]If you are ambushed during normal travel, your stamina will be at 50% (100% if sneaking).\n

			\n%c[pda_green]SNEAKING SKILL\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Your skills UI will show a new 'Sneaking' skill (%c[pda_yellow]K%c[ui_gray_2] by default).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Exp is gained by avoiding hostile encounters during travel (20 exp) or getting ambushed (10 exp).\n
			%c[pda_white]- %c[ui_gray_2]Each level adds:\n
			%c[pda_white]  - %c[pda_yellow]+3%%c[ui_gray_2] chance to avoid hostile encounters when sneaking.\n
			%c[pda_white]  - %c[pda_yellow]+2%%c[ui_gray_2] PDA sneaking progress speed (and thus reduces how much time/thirt/hunger/sleep you spend).\n
			%c[pda_white]  - %c[pda_yellow]+1 meters%c[ui_gray_2] drop distance from hostiles when ambushed (safer spawn).\n
			%c[pda_white]  - %c[pda_yellow]-3 minutes%c[ui_gray_2] to cooldown time between sneak journeys (no cooldown at max level).\n

			\n%c[pda_white]Good luck stalker...
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
